Now, we need to talk about another important movement,
さて、もう一つ重要な動きについて話さなければなりません。
which is the movement of the neural crest.
それは神経堤の動きです。
There are different types of differentiations,
分化には様々な種類があり、
of induction factors.
誘導因子も様々です。
There are factors that are purely metabolic.
純粋に代謝的な因子もあります。
There are factors that are passive.
受動的な因子もあります。
This is after neurulation.
これは神経管閉鎖の後です。
You have the vessels that will guide the system.
血管がシステムを導きます。
And then, you have everything that is genetic too,
そして、遺伝的なものもすべてあります。
which is another induction factor.
これも別の誘導因子です。
to lead to the areas where the genetic plan was made.
遺伝的に形成された領域へと導くために。
Three main types of movements.
3つの主要な動きのタイプ。
Go, prosencephalon, mesencephalon, rhombencephalon and the canal
前脳、中脳、菱脳、そして脊髄
spinal.
脊髄。
When my neural tube closes,
神経管が閉鎖すると、
I have cells that will form the neural crest.
神経堤を形成する細胞があります。
Cells that will form a lot of processes in the body.
体内で多くのプロセスを形成する細胞です。
There is like a flow from back to front, a
後ろから前へと流れがあり、
flow that will invade
その流れが
your entire face.
顔全体を覆います。
So that means that the face, the bone, the skin, up to the level of flattening, it's
つまり、顔、骨、皮膚、平坦化のレベルまで、それは
neural crest in fact.
実際には神経堤なのです。
It is a tissue that is highly informed and informative.
これは高度に情報化され、情報を提供する組織です。
Everything in your belly is neural crest.
お腹の中にあるものはすべて神経堤です。
if all these ganglia, all these little things,
もしこれらの神経節、これらの小さなものが、
well, they show you on your face what's going on inside you.
あなたの内側で起こっていることを顔に表しているとしたら。
So, you can learn to read the face, the wrinkles, the dark circles, the colors.
だから、顔、しわ、クマ、色を読むことを学ぶことができます。
I first have this prosencephalon.
まずこの前脳があります。
This prosencephalon will become telencephalon and diencephalon.
この前脳は終脳と間脳になります。
And so, you have a whole migration of the diencephalon.
そして、間脳の全体的な移動があります。
So, you have the diencephalon and the anterior mesencephalon that will migrate.
つまり、間脳と前中脳が移動します。
at the level of the neural crest.
神経堤のレベルで。
So, that means that it's a flow that happens like this and like this.
つまり、このように、そしてこのように流れるということです。
But before the neural tube closure happened,
しかし、神経管が閉鎖する前に、
there was also a negative thing, as I explained this morning.
今朝説明したように、ネガティブなものもありました。
So, it gave information related to the hepatopancreatic system,
それは肝膵臓系、
thyroid and cardiac.
甲状腺、心臓に関する情報を提供していました。
So, all of this will inform the neural crest,
これらすべてが神経堤に情報を提供します。
which is also ectomesenchyme.
これも外胚葉性間葉です。
So it's mesoderm with neural crest.
つまり、中胚葉と神経堤です。
And we see here the importance of this migration, of this colonization of
そして、この移動、この定着の重要性がここに見て取れます。
this neural crest
この神経堤は
which will inform, which will give a specific quality.
情報を提供し、特定の質を与えるでしょう。
But it will also have an impact on the construction of micro-vessels and micro
しかし、それは微小血管と特に微小神経の構築にも影響を与えるでしょう。
-nerves especially, in fact.
実際には、特に微小神経に影響を与えます。
And especially on the micro-nerves that it will influence and also on the pericytes.
そして特に微小神経と周皮細胞に影響を与えるでしょう。
It will therefore inform, it will reconstruct.
それは情報を提供し、再構築するでしょう。
Build a point of support, a point of emergence, a point of finality.
支点、出現点、最終点を構築します。
Until it gives this embryonic force to restructure as much as possible
これらのプロセス、これらの再生する微小神経を最大限に再構築するために、この胚性力を与えるまで。
But to help them, little by little.
しかし、それらを少しずつ助けるために。
And don't forget, it's at an electrical level.
そして忘れないでください、それは電気的なレベルです。
And at the level of the eye, you see, it will have the whole green side, you see, which will completely
そして目のレベルでは、緑色の側面全体が完全に包み込むでしょう。
encompass.
包み込むでしょう。
And give...
そして与える...
all this tissue here in front
ここにあるこの前方のすべての組織
which will be ectoderm,
それは外胚葉であり、
among others in relation
とりわけ関連して
with this flow
この流れと
mesodermal
中胚葉性の
around at the sclerotic level.
強膜レベルの周囲に。